All a father needs is a fighting chance.
She Rides Shotgun is a action, thriller, crime film directed by Nick Rowland.
Newly released from prison and marked for death by unrelenting enemies, Nate must
now protect his estranged 9-year-old daughter, Polly, at all costs.
With scant resources and no one to trust, Nate and Polly forge a bond under fire as he shows her
how to fight and survive—and she teaches him the true meaning of unconditional love.
Nathan Mcclusky, played by Taron Egerton.
Polly Huff, played by Ana Sophia Heger.
Charlotte, played by Odessa A'zion.
Houser, played by John Carroll Lynch.
Jimmy, played by David Lyons.
John Park, played by Rob Yang.
She Rides Shotgun is a 2025 American crime thriller film directed by Nick Rowland, written by
Jordan Harper, Ben Collins and Luke Piotrowski, and starring Taron Egerton.
It is based on Harper's 2017 novel of the same name.
It was released on August 1, 2025, by Lionsgate.
The film explores themes of based on novel or book, on the run,
aggressive, estranged daughter, father daughter relationship.
The tone is intense.